Hello guys welcome back, in this video we will
learn how you can download the insurance copy of any vehicle,
today we
will download the insurance copy from the policybazaar, if you liked the video then please
like the video and subscribe to the channel, so
here we will go to
any browser to download the insurance copy,
here I will
search google.com policybazar.com,
see their official website has come in front of me,
so simply click on it,
after going there such a dashboard will appear in front of you,
what you have to do from here is simply
click on sign in, as soon as you click on sign in,
see such a
popup will appear in front of you, what you have to do here is either
mobile number or
gmail2 is shown, so simply I
will click here, see here my vehicle
number has come, see here
one of my compressing plan is showing and
one personal accidental plan is showing,
so here I will download the compressing plan and
show it to you, so as soon as I
click on this, see here
my complete vehicle details have come and
see  If I scroll down a little, then
see here
I am getting a button to download the policy document,
so as soon as I click on it,
see a popup comes up with the copy of the downloaded policy
and the downloading starts here,
I can open it, so see,
my policy has been downloaded in front of you, the
complete details, all the
mandatory things in the document are written here, so this was all
in this video, thank
you so much for watching.